
    {
      "11":{
        "question": "What is the result of 2 + 2?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
        "answer": "4",
"id":"11"
      },
      "12":{
        "question": "What does 'NaN' stand for in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["Not a Number", "Null and None", "No Answer", "Not a Null"],
        "answer": "Not a Number","id":"12"

      },
      "13":{
        "question": "What will be logged to the console with the following code: console.log(typeof [])?",
        "options": ["Array", "Object", "Undefined", "Error"],
        "answer": "Object",
"id":"13"
      },
      "14":{
        "question": "What does 'DOM' stand for in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["Document Object Model", "Data Object Model", "Digital Object Model", "Document Oriented Model"],
        "answer": "Document Object Model", "id":"14"
      },
      "15":{
        "question": "What is the result of '5' + 3 in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["53", "8", "5", "Error"],
        "answer": "53", "id":"15"
      },
      "16":{
        "question": "What does '=== ' represent in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["Strict Equality Operator", "Type Conversion Operator", "Comparison Operator", "Assignment Operator"],
        "answer": "Strict Equality Operator", id:16
      },
      "17":{
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'push()' method in JavaScript arrays?",
        "options": ["To add elements to the beginning of an array", "To remove elements from an array", "To add elements to the end of an array", "To reverse the array"],
        "answer": "To add elements to the end of an array", "id":"17"
      },
      "18":{
        "question": "What is the default scope in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["Global Scope", "Local Scope", "Functional Scope", "Block Scope"],
        "answer": "Global Scope", "id":"18"
      },
      "19":{
        "question": "What does the 'typeof' operator return for a function in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["Function", "Object", "Undefined", "Array"],
        "answer": "Function", "id":"19"
      }, 

"20":{
        "question": "What is the result of 10 % 3 in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["1", "3", "0.3", "4"],
        "answer": "1", "id":"20"
      }
    
  }
